National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Case Files, 1988-2006, Undated; nam_apap298-1; 12.55 cubic ft.
  - Adults, 1988-2006, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1; 9 cubic ft.
    - Middlebrooks, Donald Ray (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_817 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Middleton, Frank (SC), 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_818 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Mike, Debra (AZ), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_819 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Mikeel, William (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_820 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Miles, Kenyatta (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_821 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Miles, Kevin Artice (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_822 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Miller, Donald (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_823 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Miller, Don Ray (AZ), 2000; 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_824 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Miller, Gary (TX), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_825 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Mills, Gregory (FL), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_826 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Mills, Jon Jeffrey (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_827 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Mills, Jr., John (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_828 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Mincey, Terry Michael (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_829 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Minnick, William (IN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_830 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Moeller, Donald (SD), 1992; nam_apap298-1.1_831 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Moffett, Jesse (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_832 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Monroe, Ronald (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_833 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Monterroso, Christian (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_834 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Montgomery, Williams T. (OH), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_835 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Montiel, Richard Galvan (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_836 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Montoya, Irineo (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_837 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Montoya, Ramon (TX) Executed March 25, 1993, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_838 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Moody, John (TX), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_839 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Moody, Robert Joe (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_840 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Moody, Walter LeRoy (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_841 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Moon, Richard (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_842 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - Moore, Brian Keith (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_843 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Moore, Blanche (NC), 1990; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_844 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - Moore, Carey Dean (NE), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_845 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - Moore, Charles Edward, Jr. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_846 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - Moore, Curtis (TX), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_847 (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - Moore, Frank (AR), 1996; nam_apap298-1.1_848 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Moore, Lee Edward, Jr. (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_849 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Moore, Mark (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_850 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Moore, Michael (TX), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_851 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Moore, Richard (IN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_852 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Moore, Scotty (OK), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_853 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Moore, Tyvone V. (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_854 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Moore, William (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_855 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - Moran, Richard Allan (NV) Executed April 10, 1996, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_856 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Moran, Willard (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_857 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Moreland, James (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_858 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Morelos, Vladamir Fred (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_859 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Morgan, Edward Patrick (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_860 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Morris, Kelvin (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_861 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Morrison, Jesse (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_862 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Mueller, Everett (VA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_863 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Muhammed, Yuhanni (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_864 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Mumia, Abu-Jamal (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_865 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Mumia, Abu-Jamal (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_866 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Mumia, Abu-Jamal (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_867 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Mu'Min, Dawud (VA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_868 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Muniz, Pedro (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_869 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Murphy, Mario (VA), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_870 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Murray, Robert (AZ), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_871 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Narvaiz, Leopoldo Jr. (TX) Executed June 26, 1998, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_872 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Nash, Viva Leroy (AZ), 1996; nam_apap298-1.1_873 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Nave, Emmett (MO), 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_874 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Neelley, Judith (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_875 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Nelson, David (AL), 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_876 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Nelson, Leslie (NJ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_877 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Newborn, Lorenzo (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_878 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Newton, Frances (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_879 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Nguyen,Tuan Anh (OK), 1994; 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_880 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Nichols, Harold Wayne (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_881 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Nicolaus, Robert (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_882 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Nobles, Johnathan (TX), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_883 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Noguera, William Adolf (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_884 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Noland, John (NC), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_885 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Norris, Larry (AR), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_886 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Nuncio, Paul (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_887 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Oats Jr., Soonie (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_888 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Ockenhouse, John (PA), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_889 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - O'Dell, Joseph (VA), 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_890 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Odle, James (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_891 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Oken, Steven H. (MD), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_892 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Oliver, Anthony (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_893 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - O'Malley, James Francis (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_894 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Orme, Roderick M. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_895 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - O'Rourke, Michael (AR), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_896 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Ortiz, Ignacio (AZ), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_897 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Owens, Gaille (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_898 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Owsley, Michael (MO), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_899 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Oxford, Richard (MO), 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_900 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Palma, Jimmy (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_901 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Palmer, Charles J. (NE), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_902 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Panah, Hooman Ashkan (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_903 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Pardo, Manuel (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_904 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Parker, Frank (AR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_905 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Parker, J.B, (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_906 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Parsons, Joseph (UT), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_907 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Paset, John (CT), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_908 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Patterson, Raymond (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_909 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Payne, Eric (VA), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_910 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Payne, Pervis (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_911 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Paz, Federico (ID), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_912 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Peede, Robert (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_913 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Pelzer, Kevin (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_914 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Pennington, Michael (OK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_915 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Penry, John (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_916 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Perry, Eugene (AR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_917 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Perry, James Edward (MD), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_918 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Perry, Michael O. (LA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_919 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Petary, Donald (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_920 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Peterica, Daniel (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_921 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Peterkin, Otis (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_922 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Pettit, Samuel (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_923 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Phillips, Allen Wayne (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_924 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Phillips, Richard "Speed" (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_925 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Pinholster, Scott (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_926 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Pittman, David (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_927 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Plantz, Marilyn (OK), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_928 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Plath, John (SC), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_929 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Poland, Michael (AZ), 1998; 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_930 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Poland, Patrick Gene (AZ), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_931 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Pollard, Roosevelt (MO), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_932 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Pollock, Milton (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_933 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Pope, Carlton Jerome (VA) Executed August 19, 1997, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_934 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Porter, Raleigh (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_935 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Powell, Carl Devon (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_936 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Powell, Ozie (AL), 1996; nam_apap298-1.1_937 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Powell, Reginald (MO), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_938 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Power, Robert (FL), 1990; nam_apap298-1.1_939 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Preston, Elroy (MO), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_940 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Preston, Robert (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_941 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Price, Christopher (AL), 1993; nam_apap298-1.1_942 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Prince, Cleophus Jr. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_943 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Prince, Curtis (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_944 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Provenzano, Thomas H. (FL), 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_945 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Pruet, Marion (AR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_946 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Puiatti, Carl (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_947 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Pyles, Johnny (TX) Executed June 15, 1998, nam_apap298-1.1_948 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Quesinberry, George (VA), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_949 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Quintanilla, Jessie (Military), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_950 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Quintero, Derrick (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_951 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Ragon, Derrick (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_952 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Rainey, Michael (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_953 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Raley, David Allen (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_954 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Ramdass, Bobby Lee (VA), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_955 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Ramirez, Richard (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_956 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Ramsey, Roy (MO), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_957 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Ransom, Kenneth (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_958 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Ray, Johnny Babe Jr. (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_959 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Reams, Kenneth (AR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_960 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Rector, Charles (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_961 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Rector, Ricky (AR), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_962 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Red Dog, James A. (DE), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_963 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Reese, John (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_964 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Reeves, Randolph (NE), 1996; 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_965 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Reid, Anthony (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_966 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Reid, Lloyd (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_967 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Remata, Daniel (FL), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_968 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Renfro, Steven C. (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_969 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Reyes, Angel (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_970 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Rice, David L. (WA), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_971 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Rich, Darrell (CA), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_972 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Richardson, Antonio (MO), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_973 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Richardson, Miguel (TX), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_974 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Richey, Kenneth T. (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_975 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Richley, Darryl V. (AR) Executed August 3, 1994, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_976 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Riddle, Ernest M. (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_977 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Riechmann, Dieter (FL), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_978 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Riggs, Christina (AR), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_979 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Riley, James (DE), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_980 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Riley, Leandress (CA), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_981 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Riley, Michael (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Ring, Timothy (AZ), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Rios, Miguel (PA), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Rivera, Michael (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Rivers, Delores (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Roach, Steven (VA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Robb, Jason (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Robbins, Malcolm (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Robedeaux, James (OK), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Roberts, Michael Donald (OK), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Roberts, Rickey (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Roberts, Roy (MO), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_993 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Roberts, Sammy D. (SC) September 25, 1998, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Robertson, Andrew E. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Robinson, Antyane (PA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Robinson, James, Jr. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_997 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Robison, Larry (TX), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Roche, Charles E. Jr (IN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_999 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Rocheville, David (SC), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1000 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Rodrigues, Jose A. (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1001 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Rodrigues, Luis (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1002 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Rodriguez, Frank (CO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1003 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Rodriguez, Toribio R. (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1004 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Rogers, Dayton Leroy (OR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1005 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Rogers, Glen (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1006 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Rogers, Kelly (OK), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_1007 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Rogers, Patrick (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1008 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Rogovich, Pete Carl (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1009 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Rojem, Richard Norman (OK), 1993; nam_apap298-1.1_1010 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Rolan, Florencio (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1011 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Roldan, Ricardo (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1012 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Rolling, Danny (FL), 1993; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1013 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Romano, John (OK), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1014 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Rompilla, Ronald (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1015 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Rose, James (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1016 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Rose, Milo (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1017 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Ross, Arthur M. (AZ), 1998; nam_apap298-1.1_1018 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Ross, Bobby (OK), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1019 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Ross, Michael Bruce (CT), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1020 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Routier, Darlie (TX), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1021 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Rowland, Guy Kevin (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1022 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Royal, Thomas (VA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_1023 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Roybal, Rudolph (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1024 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Ruescher, ED (MO), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1025 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Ruiz, Alejandro Gilbert (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1026 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Running, Eagle, Sean Bernard (AZ), 1993; nam_apap298-1.1_1027 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Russell, Willie C. (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1028 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Ryan, Michael (NE), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1029 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Sagastegui, Jeremy V. (WA), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1030 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Salazar, Maximo (OK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1031 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Salcido, Ramon (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1032 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Samuels, Mary (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1033 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Sanborn, Paramore (KY), 1991; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1034 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Sanchez-Velasco, Rigoberto (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1035 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Sanders, Raymond (AR), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1036 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Sanders, Reginald N. (DE), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_1037 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Sanders, Ronald (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1038 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Sanderson, Ricky L. (NC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1039 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Sandoval, Alfred (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1040 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Santellan, Jose (TX), 2002; nam_apap298-1.1_1041 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Santiago, Salvador Carlos (PA), 1992; nam_apap298-1.1_1042 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Saranchek, Daniel (PA), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1043 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Sasser, Andrew (AR), 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1044 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Satcher, Michael C. (VA) Executed December 9, 1997, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1045 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Saunders, William (VA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_1046 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Savino, Joseph (VA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1047 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Saylor, Benny (IN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1048 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Scanlon, Donald (NC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1049 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Schurz, Eldon M. (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1050 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Schwab, Mark (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1051 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Scott, Jay D. (OH), 2001; 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_1052 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Scott, Paul (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1053 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Sexton, Michael Earl (NC), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1054 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Sharp, Michael (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1055 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Shaw, Bobby L. (MO), 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1056 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Sheldon, Jeffrey (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1057 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Shelton, Steven (DE), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1058 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Shepard, Mark (VA), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_1059 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Shepphard, Bobby Terrell (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1060 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Sheridan, Darrell (AR), 1993; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1061 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Shields, Robert (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1062 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Sibley, George (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1063 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Silva, Benjamin Wai (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1064 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Simon, Robert Jr. (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1065 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Sims, Mitchell (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1066 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Sims, Terry Melvin (SC), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1067 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Singleton, Charles (AR), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1068 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Singleton, Fred (SC), 2005; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1069 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Sireci, Henry (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1070 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Siripongs, Jaturun (CA), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1071 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Six, Andrew (MO), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1072 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Skaggs, David (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1073 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Slaughter, James Earl (KY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1074 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Slaughter, Michael Corey (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1075 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Slawson, Newton Carlton (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1076 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Smallwood, Dion (OK), 2000; nam_apap298-1.1_1077 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Smith, Andrew (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1078 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Smith, Brian (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1079 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Smith, Bruce (VA), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1080 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Smith, Clay (AR), 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_1081 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Smith, Clifford (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1082 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Smith, Frank E. (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1083 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Smith, Frank Lee (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1084 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Smith, Gregory Scott (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1085 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Smith, James Edward (TX), 2005; nam_apap298-1.1_1086 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Smith, James W. (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1087 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Smith, Joe (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1088 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Smith, John Eldon (GA) Executed December 15, 1983, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1089 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Smith, Oscar (TN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1090 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Smith, Phillip D. (OK), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1091 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Smith, Rickie (TX), 1999; nam_apap298-1.1_1092 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Smith, Robert Douglas (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1093 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Smith, Robert (IN), 1998; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1094 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Smith, Roderick Lynn (OK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1095 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Smith, Samuel (MO), 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1096 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Smith, Tommie (IN), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1097 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Smith, William H. (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1098 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Smith, Willie Albert (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1099 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Snell, Richard W. (AR) Executed April 19, 1995, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1100 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Socher, Dennis (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1101 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Sockwell, Michael (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1102 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Soloman, Morris (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1103 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - South, Robert W. (SC) Executed May 31, 1996, Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1104 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Sowell, Billie J. (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1105 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Spann, Sterling (SC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1106 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Spence, David (TX), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1107 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Spencer, Clinton L. (AZ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1108 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Spinelli, Juanita (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1109 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Spirko, John (OH), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1110 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Spivey, Ronald (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1111 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Spotz, Mark (PA), 1999; 2001; nam_apap298-1.1_1112 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Stager, Barbara (NC), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1113 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Stanely, Gerald Frank (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1114 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Stankewitz, Douglas (CA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1115 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Stano, Gerald (FL), 1997; Undated; nam_apap298-1.1_1116 (Box 8, Folder 135)